

Human resources representative with experience managing employee benefits, employee hiring and onboarding, performance management and HR records. Reliable and organized team member with the ability to communicate effectively and handle office changes. Skilled at building and maintaining relationships, representing shared company values and managing employees across all levels of an organization.

Dedicated educator with more than 5 Years' experience as a Teacher. Proven superior ability to manage classrooms and give effective lectures. Skilled at applying behavior modification strategies. Able to cooperate with other teachers, administrators, and specialists.

CONTACT

PHONE: 0315-88-28-768

EMAIL: Syedabdi556@gmail.com

ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS

- Microsoft word "Skillful"
- Management Skills "Skillful"
- Assignment Writer "Experienced"
- Content Writer "Experienced"
- Behavior modification "Experienced"
- Teaching, tutoring and counseling "Skillful"
- Positive atmosphere promotion "Expert"
- Calm under pressure "Experienced"
- Reporting and documentation"Expert"
- Critical thinker "Expert"

SYED KUMAIL MUSTAFA

WORK EXPERIENCE

TAG Group. Apr-21-Present

HR Executive | Tenure: Jan 2022 to Present

- ✓ Recruiting, training and developing staff
- ✓ Conducting Initial Interviews
- ✓ Approving job descriptions and advertisements
- ✓ Looking after the health, safety and welfare of all employees
- ✓ Organizing staff training sessions and activities
- ✓ Monitoring staff performance and attendance
- ✓ Advising line managers and other employees on employment law and the employer's
 own employment policies and procedures
- ✓ Negotiating salaries, contracts, working conditions or redundancy packages with staff and representatives.

Sr. HR Officer | Tenure: Oct 2021 to Dec 2021

- ✓ Recruiting, training and developing staff
- ✓ Conducting Initial Interviews
- ✓ Looking after the health, safety and welfare of all employees
- ✓ Assisting in Payroll and make sure staff is getting paid on timely basis

HR Officer | Tenure: July 2021 to Oct 2021

- ✓ Assisting in Recruiting, training and developing staff
- ✓ Conducting Initial calling interviews for screenings.
- ✓ Organizing staff training sessions and activities

HR cum Admin | Tenure: Apr 2021 to Jun 2021

- ✓ Organize and maintain personnel records
- ✓ Update internal databases (e.g. record sick or maternity leave)
- ✓ Answer employees queries about HR-related issues
- ✓ Assist payroll department by providing relevant employee information (e.g. leaves of absence, sick days and work schedules)
- ✓ Participate in HR projects (e.g. help organize a job fair event)

White House Grammar School [Coordinator]

Jan-20-Apr 22

- ✓ Working in Management with different responsibilities;
- ✓ Ensuring the policies directed by Head office are being followed.
- ✓ Organizing the schedule
- ✓ Take disciplinary actions when necessary
- ✓ Reporting the situation back to head office
- ✓ Worked as a Physics team leader in an Inter-School Physics League "PSL" among different campus of WHGS.
- ✓ Teaching and educating students according to their academics needs, abilities.
- Marking, correcting and giving feedback on the work done by the students.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2019 University of Karachi ✓ Specialization "Parasitology" ✓ Major in Subject: "Zoology" ✓ Completed coursework in Pathology, Hematology etc. ✓ Awarded with 1st Division. 2015 - 2018 University of Karachi ✓ Major in Subject "Zoology" ✓ Minor in Subject "Biochemistry and Physiology" ✓ Completed course work in various branches of Biology including "Anatomy, Histology, and Genetics etc." ✓ Awarded with 1st Division 2011 - 2014 P.E.C.H.S Govt. Degree Science College ✓ H.S.C completed with Pre-Medical 2006 - 2011 **Rangers Public School and College** ✓ S.S.C completed with Science

LANGUAGE

English — B2

REFERENCE

Available only upon request